Guide to the Arlene Gottfried Photographs 1972-1994 PR 473
New-York Historical Society
Arlene Gottfried photographs
1972-1994
New-York Historical Society
Gottfried, Arlene
PR 473
4 Linear feet in 7 boxes
This collection consists of 325 photographs by New York City street photographer Arlene Gottfried (1950–2017). The images, which include color and black & white prints, offer dynamic portraits and scenes of daily life in ethnically diverse communities in New York City from 1972-1994.
Arrangement
The photographs are arranged alphabetically by title.
Biographical / Historical
Arlene Gottfried (1950–2017) was a New York City street photographer who captured the grit and vibrancy of New York in the last decades of the 20th century.
Born August 26, 1950 in Coney Island, Brooklyn, she was the daughter of Lillian (Zimmerman) and Max Gottfried, who owned a hardware store above which the family lived. Gottfried was the older sister of comedian and actor Gilbert Gottfried (1955–2022) and Karen Gottfried. When Gottfried was 9, the family moved to Crown Heights, Brooklyn, and then in the 1970s, they moved to Manhattan's Lower East Side. As an adult, Arlene Gottfried lived in Westbeth Artists Housing, a subsidized artist community in Greenwich Village.
After studying photography at the Fashion Institute of Technology, Gottfried worked as a photographer for an advertising agency. She then worked as a freelance photographer for publications such as The New York Times Magazine, Fortune, Life, and the Village Voice. Gottfried published five books of her work: The Eternal Light (1999), Midnight (2003), Sometimes Overwhelming (2008), Bacalaitos and Fireworks (2011), and Mommie: Three Generations of Women (2015). In 2025, the New York Historical presented an exhibition entitled Picture Stories: Photographs by Arlene Gottfried.
Gottfried died at home in New York City on August 8, 2017.
Access Restrictions
Materials in this collection may be stored offsite. For more information on making arrangements to consult them, please visit www.nyhistory.org/library/visit.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Dara Gottfried and Karen Gottfried, 2024. (299 photos)
Gift of Sally Klingenstein Martell, 2024. (26 photos)
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of 325 photographs by New York City street photographer Arlene Gottfried (1950–2017). The majority are silver gelatin prints, along with some color cibachrome prints. The photos date from 1972-1994.
Gottfried's photographs document the people and places of 1970s and 1980s New York City. They include portraits of her family, friends, neighbors, and people she encountered in ethnically diverse communities across the city. Settings include apartment interiors, churches, festivals, block parties, parades, beaches, Coney Island amusement parks, sidewalks, vacant lots, nightclubs, roller rinks, and discos.
The titles and dates were derived from labels on the photographs, and from information provided by the donors. Item numbers were assigned during processing.
Children -- New York (State) -- New York -- Photographs.; Drag queens; Nightclubs; Nightlife -- New York (State) -- New York.; Portrait photography -- New York (State) -- New York.; Street photography -- New York (State) -- New York.; Color photographs.; Black-and-white photographs.
- 3 Men with Afros (Box 2, Item 1)
- Actor with Wrinkled Jacket Hands in Pockets (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 2)
- After the Show, Staten Island (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 3)
- Amores (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 4)
  Scope and Contents
  Cibachrome print.
- Angel & Woman, on Boardwalk Brighton Beach (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 5)
- Angel Garcia (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 6)
- Ann Magnuson on Stairwell (Box 4, Item 7)
- Argument on Riis Beach, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 8)
- Avenue C Bodega (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 9)
- Baby Boy on Large Chair (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 10)
- Baby in Crib (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 11)
- Baby in Overalls (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 12)
- Baby Paper Bag Hat, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1, Item 13)
- Backstage, Xenon (Box 3, Item 14)
- Ballerina, Halloween Parade, Westbeth (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 15)
- Bar on Fire Island, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 16)
- Be My Valentine, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 17)
- Bethesda Fountain, Puerto Rican Day Parade (Box 7, Item 18)
- Bill Cosby on TV (Box 7, Item 19)
- Block Party on East 7th Street (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 20)
- Bodybuilding Competition at Washington Irving High School (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 21)
- Botticelli Girl, Fire Island, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 22)
- Boxer Boy (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 23)
- Boxer Joe Fraser (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 24)
- Boxer Stance (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 25)
- Boy and his Chicken (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 26)
- Boy and his Chicken two (Box 5, Folder 2, Item 27)
- Boy Drinking from Water Fountain (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 28)
- Boy in Bathing Suit (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 29)
- Boy in Car on Purim (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 30)
- Boy in Front of Chain Fence (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 31)
- Boy in Go Cart in Park (Box 7, Item 32)
- Boy on School Bus (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 33)
- Boy Under a Bridge (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 34)
- Boy with Afro on Bicycle in front of Trash Cans (Box 3, Item 35)
- Boy with Feather (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 36)
- Boy with Hat in front of Trash Cans (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 37)
- Boy with his Grandfather (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 38)
- Boy with his Grandfather Party with Relatives (Box 5, Folder 3, Item 39)
- Boy with key around neck (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 40)
- Boy with leather jacket, sunglasses and a cigarette (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 41)
- Boys hanging out on Box Cars (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 42)
- Brazilian Carnival, Waldorf Astoria (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 43)
- Brothers with Their Vines, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 44)
- Bubbie Dancer (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 45)
- Bubbie Sitting on a Bed (Box 7, Item 46)
- Buick, East 6th Street (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 47)
- Butcher's Boy (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 48)
- Charles and son Leon at Home (Box 7, Item 49)
- Charlies Fish Market (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 50)
- Chihuahuas (Box 5, Folder 4, Item 51)
- Choir on Broken Bus, 1993 (Box 7, Item 52)
- Cinderella, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 53)
- Clown 1, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 54)
- Coney Island Basketball (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 55)
- Coney Island Couple Carrying Bags (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 56)
- Coney Island Hug (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 57)
- Coney Island Man with Broken Arm (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 58)
- Continental Foods (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 59)
- Coquito (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 60)
- Couple Costumes (Box 5, Folder 5, Item 61)
- Couple Fancy Night Out, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 62)
- Couple in bed holding purse (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 63)
- Couple Kissing holding cigarettes (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 64)
- Couple on Staten Island Ferry (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 65)
- Couple smoking at Coney Island (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 66)
- Cowgirl Crotch - Paradise Garage (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 67)
- Dance A Thon (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 68)
- Dancer with feathers in front of wallpaper, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 69)
- Danger at Le Clique (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 70)
- Danger, Women, Monkey, and Banana at Le Clique, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 6, Item 71)
- Debbie Harry Lookalike, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 72)
- Diamond Lil's, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 73)
- Disco Grannie at Studio 54 (Box 3, Item 74)
- Doorway in Brooklyn (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 75)
- Doorway in Soho (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 76)
- Drag Dancer Squat (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 77)
- Drag in Bra with lips (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 78)
- Drag Queen Reclining on Chair (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 79)
- Drag Show in Restaurant, Staten Island, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 80)
- Drag with fishnet hat, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 81)
- Drag with makeup in sweater, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 7, Item 82)
- Dying of AIDS - Please Help (Box 1, Item 83)
- East 110th Street (Box 3, Item 84)
- Eddie Sun's Friend Ironing (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 85)
- El Pico, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 86)
- ELC's Group Portrait, Appreciation Service La Gree Baptist (Box 7, Item 87)
  Cibachrome print. ELC=Eternal Light Choir.
- Elvira Madigan Dress (Box 3, Item 88)
- Eternal Light Choir Performing (Box 1, Item 89)
- Eyes, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 90)
- Family behind Screen (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 91)
- Family in Coney Island blowing bubble (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 92)
- Family with Stroller (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 93)
- Family with Two Daughters (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 94)
- Father with Daughter Portrait (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 95)
- Flying Man at Le Clique (Box 3, Item 96)
- Fort Apache, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 97)
- George Rossovich Walks Out, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8, Item 98)
- Gerri & Keenan at Church on Thanksgiving Day (Box 7, Item 99)
- Giant Dildo Les Monches Party, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 100)
- Girl in Church with lace on head (Box 7, Item 101)
- Girl leaning on car showing a little tit, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 102)
- Girl on a School Bus, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 103)
- Girl with Crown (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 104)
- Girl with Crown and Baton (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 105)
- Girl with Giant Glasses (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 106)
- Gospel Singer (Box 7, Item 107)
- Grandmother and Grandson in Chinatown (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 108)
- Grant's Tomb (Box 7, Item 109)
- Guy With Radio East 7th Street (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 110)
- Halloween (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 111)
- Halloween Parade in Greenwich Village, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 9, Item 112)
- Hand Shake (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 113)
- Hassid on Riis Nude Bay Beach (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 114)
- Helmet, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 115)
- Hispanic Man on Motorcycle (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 116)
- Hispanic Woman Long Hair Portrait, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 117)
- Homeless 80's Punk Woman Passed Out (Box 7, Item 118)
- I Love Johnny (Box 7, Item 119)
- Interracial Couple (Box 7, Item 120)
- Iris Praises the Lord - Harlem, 1991 (Box 7, Item 121)
- Irma Rivera and Family (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 122)
- Isabel Croft Jumping Rope, Brooklyn (Box 3, Item 123)
- Jeffrey and the Twins at Home - Coney Island, NY, 1993 (Box 7, Item 124)
- Jeffrey's Cousins at Mommie's 70th Birthday Party (Box 7, Item 125)
- Jigaboo at Empire Rollerdome (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 126)
  The "Jigaboo Jammers" was a New York City roller disco group founded in the late 1970s by Vincent "Vinzerrelli" Brown of Jamaica Queens.
- Johnny Cintron, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 127)
- Johnny Cintron wearing wedding ring, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 128)
- Johnny Colon's Music School, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10, Item 129)
- Junkee with belt and Afro (Box 5, Folder 10, Item 130)
- Karen sitting in a club chair (Box 7, Item 131)
- Kavarro US Army Woman Soldier, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 132)
- Kid and Target (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 133)
- Kids looking through Chain Link Fence (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 134)
- Kids on a Stoop (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 135)
- Kids talking to old Lady on the Beach (Box 1, Folder 11, Item 136)
- Kish Manasse's Photography Studio, Fifth Avenue, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 137)
- KISS, Halloween Parade, Westbeth (Box 2, Item 138)
- Kissing on the Highway, Queens (Box 4, Item 139)
- La Blusa Rosa (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 140)
- La Marqueta, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 141)
- Latino Teen Boy in Bed with Knife, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 142)
- Lesbian Black Women Riis Beach (Box 5, Folder 11, Item 143)
- Lillian hands together (Box 7, Item 144)
- Little Girl Dressed as Princess, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 145)
- Lloyd Steir and Dogs at the Big Apple Circus (Box 4, Item 146)
- Loss, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 147)
- Luke Silverman, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 148)
- Man Carrying Baby on New Years (Box 7, Item 150)
- Man wearing underwear with mustache (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 151)
- Man with Cowbot hat and punk sunglasses with splattered shirt, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 152)
- Man with Pipe and his Grandson (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 153)
- Marsha P. Johnson and young boy with roses (Box 3, Item 154)
- Men's Room at Disco, 1978 (Box 2, Item 155)
- Midnight at desk with lamp (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 157)
- Midnight by Door with Halloween Costume Hanging, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 158)
- Midnight close up (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 159)
- Midnight close up portrait (Box 5, Folder 12, Item 160)
- Midnight close up face (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 161)
- Midnight Cowboy Hat on Bed (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 162)
- Midnight drinking from a teapot (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 163)
- Midnight Funeral (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 164)
- Midnight Hospitalized and behind a metal screen (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 165)
- Midnight in bed with a Teddy Bear (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 166)
- Midnight in Bed, 1980s (Box 4, Item 167)
- Midnight in Robe by Window (Box 4, Item 168)
- Midnight rolling on bed with stockings (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 169)
- Midnight shaved head and earring (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 170)
- Midnight Shirtless Playing Pots in Kitchen (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 171)
- Midnight sitting on a chair in the kitchen next to stove (Box 6, Folder 1, Item 172)
- Midnight sitting on the bathroom floor (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 173)
- Midnight sitting with necklace and red shirt (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 174)
- Midnight Sleeping with Red Shirt (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 175)
- Midnight with beanie and coat (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 176)
- Midnight with Party Horn (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 177)
- Midnight with Red Cowboy Hat and Face Covered (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 178)
- Midnight, Sunlight on One Eye (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 179)
- Miguel Algarin Eulogizes Ritchie Cruz (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 180)
- Miguel Pinero counting money (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 181)
- Miguel Pinero Fort Apache Sitting by Open Window (Box 6, Folder 2, Item 182)
- Miguel Pinero Overcoat (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 183)
- Miguel Pinero with Boy Holding Knife, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 184)
- Miguel Pinero, Avenue D (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 185)
- Miguel Pinero, Avenue D, Shadows (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 186)
- Mommie Kissing Bubbie Delancey St. (Box 4, Item 187)
- Mommie Reading with Magnifying Glass (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 188)
- Mommie Sitting on Balcony Lower East Side, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 189)
- Monique and Michell Support Barbara in Rehearsal, Harlem, NY, 1991 (Box 7, Item 190)
- Monique and Tamar take a Bath on a Saturday Morning (Box 7, Item 191)
- Monique Hugging Kayua, La Gree Baptist Church, Harlem NY, 1991 (Box 7, Item 192)
- Monique of the Love Fellowship Crusade Choir (Box 7, Item 193)
- Monique's Daughter with Doll (Box 1, Item 194)
- Monique's Daughter's Funeral (Box 7, Item 195)
- Monique's son Tamar has a Birthday Party, Bronx, NY, 1994 (Box 7, Item 196)
- Mother and Baby Yawning (Box 4, Item 197)
- Mother and Child (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 198)
- Mother and Daughter Sleeping (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 199)
- Mother in Polka Dot Pants Dancing (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 200)
- Mother introducing Baby to Group of Kids (Box 6, Folder 3, Item 201)
- Mouths Open Central Park, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 202)
- Nelson Rivera, Tornado Roller Coaster, Coney Island, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 205)
- New York City Skyline, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 206)
- No Wheels (Box 2, Item 207)
- Ocean Beach Gay Couple (Box 2, Item 208)
- Ocean Beach Gay Couple Holding Balls, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 209)
- Older Couple with Painted Eyebrows (Box 7, Item 210)
- Parade Two Women and a Girl, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 211)
- Pete's Sister in Law (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 212)
- Photographer on Beach selling photos, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 4, Item 213)
- Pituka at Bethesda Fountain (Box 4, Item 214)
- Playin Around (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 215)
- Playin Around Two (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 216)
- Pocono Rollerdome with Whistle (Box 6, Folder 4, Item 217)
- Polar Express, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 218)
- Pop Choir Manager on his Birthday, 1991 (Box 7, Item 219)
- Portrait in front of Albums, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 220)
- Portrait of young man at Empire Rollerdome (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 221)
- Portrait Young Man Plaid Shirt with hat (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 222)
- Praying on the street (Box 7, Item 223)
- Pregnant woman in Dressing Room (Box 7, Item 224)
- Puerto Rican Day Parade (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 225)
- Puerto Rican Day Parade, New York, 1981 (Box 1, Item 226)
- Puerto Rican Day Parade, Woman with Rollers (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 227)
- Pug Dog Show at Alice Austen's House, Staten Island (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 228)
- Punk Girl with Umbrella on Subway Stairs, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 229)
- Punk Guy with Nose Ring and Chain (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 230)
- Purim in Brooklyn (Box 7, Item 231)
- Red High Heel Shoes with Long Shadow (Box 6, Folder 5, Item 232)
- Reflection in the Mirror (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 233)
- Rick James with Two Women in Furs, 1981 (Box 2, Item 234)
- Ricky in Coney Island (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 235)
- Riis Beach Portrait Black Man Arms Behind Head (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 236)
- Riis Nude Bay, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 237)
- Rikers Island Olympics, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 238)
- Rock and Roll Couple, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 239)
- Rockette, Radio City Music Hall, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 240)
- Rockettes, Radio City Music Hall, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 241)
- Rose Katz on the Pier at Coney Island, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 242)
- Roseland Ballroom, 1980 [1983] (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 243)
- Roseland Ballroom, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 6, Item 244)
- Sad Clown Mask (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 245)
- Sailor Boy (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 246)
- Savage Riders, Baby's Eyes Closed and Yawning (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 247)
- Savage Riders at the Puerto Rican Day Parade (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 248)
- Secret, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 249)
- Selwyn in Brooklyn Giving the Pitch (Box 7, Item 250)
- Selwyn Laughing on Bus (Box 7, Item 251)
- Selwyn on E. 125th St. (Box 7, Item 252)
- Selwyn on the Street in Leather Coat, Brooklyn, NY, 1994 (Box 7, Item 253)
- Selwyn Sleeping on Bus (Box 7, Item 254)
- Selwyn's Funeral, La Gree Baptist Church, November 1995 (Box 7, Item 255)
- Shirtless Tattooed Man with Bird and Stick, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 256)
- Showgirl in Front of Swan (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 257)
- Showgirl with feather skirt [2 copies] (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 258)
- Skip [2 copies], 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7, Item 259)
- Street Photographer (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 260)
- Striped Woman at Studio 54 (Box 3, Item 261)
- Sunshine Social Club, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 262)
- Teddy Bear (Box 1, Folder 8, Item 263)
- Teen Boy with coat and necklace (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 264)
- Teenage Boy with long hair and cigarette (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 265)
- Teenagers and Cotton Candy, Coney Island (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 266)
- The Eternal Light Singers (Box 7, Item 267)
- The Last Jump, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 268)
- Three boys in a neighborhood (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 269)
- Three Generations, Bubbie, Mommie, and Gilbert (Box 4, Item 270)
- Threesome dancing in club, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 271)
- Tim Fine, His Mother, and her poodle, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 272)
- Topless Large Woman on Beach (Box 7, Item 273)
- Topless Woman Wearing Leather and Boots in Nightclub, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 8, Item 274)
- Topless Woman with Sunglasses and Skirt, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 275)
- Topless Woman with White Gloves, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 276)
- Trampoline, 1984 (Box 4, Item 277)
- Tricycle on Boardwalk, Brighton Beach, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 278)
- Triplets (Box 7, Item 279)
- Two Boys and Chicken Pens, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 280)
- Two Drag Queens and a Woman, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 281)
- Two Men with Afros, Gay Day in Central Park (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 282)
- Two Men with Jesus Poster (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 283)
- Two Naked Toddlers on the Beach (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 284)
- Two Teenage Girls (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 285)
- Two Women touching breasts, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 286)
- Two Women holding photo strips, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9, Item 287)
- Two Young Men hanging on a Pole (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 288)
- Under the Boardwalk (Box 4, Item 289)
- Veteran's Day Parade (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 290)
- Vivian, Riis Beach, New York, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 291)
- Waiting for Train (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 292)
- Wedding Party in Connecticut (Box 4, Item 293)
- Westchester Car Show Bikers (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 294)
- Wild Night with Two Women and One Man (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 295)
- Wolverine Camp, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 296)
- Woman at Lounge, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 297)
- Woman at lunch counter with cigarette (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 298)
- Woman at Marilyn Monroe Look-a-like Contest Posing, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 299)
- Woman at Marilyn Monroe Look-a-like Contest, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 10, Item 300)
- Woman Clown (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 301)
- Woman feeding baby, El Barrio (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 302)
- Woman in Front of Old Car at Auto Shop (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 303)
- Woman on ground with Roller Skates (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 304)
- Woman on Subway (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 305)
- Woman showing One Breast, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 306)
- Woman showing one breast next to Milk (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 307)
- Woman under a Leaf, Tompkins Square Park, New York, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 308)
- Woman Vampire in Halloween Parade, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 309)
- Woman Wearing Sneakers, Coney Island, 1976 (Box 3, Item 310)
- Woman with bandaged nose (Box 7, Item 311)
- Woman with Dogs in Central Park, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 312)
- Woman with Pig Tails, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 11, Item 313)
- Woman with Roller Skates, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 314)
- Woman with tank dress under tree (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 315)
- Woman with Towel at Rikers Island, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 316)
- Woman with Veil and Cross Sitting by Window, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 317)
- Young Girl holding red skirt, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 318)
- Young Girl Holding Dog in Blanket, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 319)
- Young Girl in Front of Man with Tattoo "Irma R. Rivera" on Back, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 320)
- Young Girls by Chain Link Fence (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 321)
- Young Man in Powder Blue Suit Jacket (Box 7, Item 322)
- Young Man Posing in front of Bicycle (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 323)
- Young Man topless with face paint, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 324)
- Young Man with heavy makeup (Box 6, Folder 12, Item 325)
- Untitled [Four boys playing on sidewalk] (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 149)
- Untitled [Man with flames] (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 156)
- Untitled [Man with needle and knife], 1982 (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 203)
- Untitled [Two men, one wearing a cap] (Box 6, Folder 13, Item 204)